<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application64</string>
    <string name="this_is_another_activity">This is another Activity2</string>
    <string name="this_is_first_activity">This is first Activity</string>
    <string name="start_another_activity">Start Another Activity</string>


    <string name="display_one">Costa Rica occupies a privileged place in the heart of Central
        America for the richness of its beaches, comprises 1,228 km of coastline, of which 1,016 km
        are from the Pacific coast and 212 km in the Caribbean Sea, you are separated by
        just three hours in vehicle or 45 minutes by air from San José. It is estimated that 600
        beaches surround the entire national territory. This wealth allows the enjoyment of the
        beach as a means of recreation, sport and rest. These are wooded beaches, with natural
        spaces and relatively little influx of tourists.
        The Caribbean region stands out for its variety of marine ecosystems and its white- and
        black-sand beaches, ideal for activities centered around nature and the ocean, including
        surfing, diving in clear water, basking in the sun and hiking along the coast.</string>

    <string name="display_two">When visiting any beach in Costa Rica, keep the following security
        precautions in mind: Take care of your belongings while enjoying the sea or leave them
        somewhere they can be watched. Always use sunscreen to avoid burns on your skin. When
        possible, do not swim on your own and consult the authorities regarding beach conditions.
        Be aware of warning flags on the beach. Do not enter the ocean if you do not know how to
        swim. If surfing as a beginner, always be accompanied by an instructor.</string>

    <string name="display_three">The Pacific coast contains major tourism centers and beaches
        that are favorites among surfers, including Esterillos, Jacó, Hermosa, Boca Barranca,
        as well as the Pavones Sector and the surroundings of the Marino Ballena National Park,
        with its famous long left wave. Near the beach areas you will find a wide variety of options
        to stay and taste Costa Rican cuisine. Among the variety of hotels you can enjoy are:
        all inclusive option, honeymoon hotels, eco resort, family hotels, 5 star hotels, etc.
        In addition to the typical food you can also enjoy restaurants that specialize
        in international dishes.</string>
</resources>